Afrazahmed Momin

Pune, India

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/afrazm7

988 124 2787

https://github.com/afrazchelsea



Final Year Engineering Student. Love to code and have a strong hold on Data Structures and Algorithms. Have worked on iOS as well as Android platforms previously. Working towards becoming a Full Stack Developer soon. Big ML / Al enthusiast.



Work History

2019-06 - 2019-07

Data Science Intern

Tech Smart Systems, Pune, Maharashtra

- Learnt Python from scratch
- Worked with various Machine Learning algorithms to create the best working models
- Got familiar with data visualization and performed data analysis on multiple projects

2019-01 - 2019-03

2016-05 - 2016-08

Intern

Toppr, Pune, Maharashtra

- Worked on Quality Analysis
- Got familiar with Periscope Data and helped the team analyse the data effectively
- Worked closely with the knowledge team

Software Development Intern

Synepis, Pune, Maharashtra

- Worked with Objective C to create iOS applications
- Helped design the UI for the same applications
- Worked with Parse for database integration



Skills

Good with Data Structures and Algorithms

Well versed with C, C++, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP

Android / iOS Application Development

Working on my ML / Data Science skillset



Education

2016-08 - Current

Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Engineering

Sinhgad Academy of Enigneering - Pune University (SPPU)

SSC - 91.80% : HSC- 74.62% Rosary High School - Camp, Pune